你把我放了，我是沃尔特·塞缪尔，如果我能打电话给你。
You put me, I'm Walter Samuel, if I can call you.
Me pones, soy Walter Samuel, si puedo llamarte.
在那里，您说...零吃了五秒钟，妈妈。
And there you said ... zero eats five seconds, and mommy.
Y ahí dijiste... Cero coma cinco segundos, ya mami.
0'05秒。
0'05 seconds.
0'05 segundos.
我认为我们都是专业人士，我们集中精力...
I think we are both professionals and we focus ...
Creo que los dos somos profesionales y nos centramos...
我们与马德里的亚特里奇托精神一起工作，我们工作。
We are with the Atlético spirit of Madrid and we work.
Estamos con el Espíritu Atlético de Madrid y trabajamos.
我一进入Cerro del Espino ...
As soon as I enter the Cerro del Espino ...
En cuanto entro al Cerro del Espino...
他是马德里体育教练。
He is the Madrid athletic coach.
Es el entrenador del Atletico de Madrid.
朱利安，你在做什么？
What are you doing, Julian?
¿Qué haces, Juliano?
一切好吗？
All good?
¿Todo bien?
好的？
GOOD?
¿Bien?
安静的？
Quiet?
¿Tranquilo?
是的，是的，是的。
Yes, yes, yes.
Sí, sí, sí.
这是你的真正房子。
This is your real house.
Esta es tu casa de verdad.
当我说您的房子时，我说的是Lety，可以说。
When I say your house, I'm talking about the Lety, let's say.
Cuando digo tu casa, estoy hablando de la Lety, digamos.
这是你的家。
It's your home.
Es tu casa.
是的，是的。
Yes, yes.
Sí, sí.
事实，当我的老人带给我时，很小的事...
The truth, from very small, when my old man brought me ...
La verdad, desde muy chiquito, cuando mi viejo me traía...
在这里，我怀里有那张照片。
Here, I had that photo in my arms.
acá, que me tenía en brazos esa foto.
是的，这是我的房子。
Yes, this is my house.
Sí, esta es mi casa.
当您坐此笔记时，我想知道您是否已经在这里服装了，您来了。
When you sat this note, I wondered if you already, for example, of the costume here, you came running.
Yo, cuando te sentaste esta nota, me preguntaba si vos ya, por ejemplo, del vestuario acá, viniste corriendo.
在球场上，让一切都是如此，因为您将其充分地交付到了一切中。
on the court and gives the feeling that everything is so because you deliver it to the fullest in everything.
en la cancha y da la sensación de que todo es así porque la entregas al máximo en todo.
您也是如此，就像在法庭上一样吗？
Are you so in life too, as in the court?
¿Sos así en la vida también, como en la cancha?
是的，通常在我的生活中，我非常...
Yes, usually in my life I am very ...
Sí, generalmente en mi vida soy muy...
活跃，非常激烈，我以这种方式生活。
Active, very intense, I live that way.
activo, muy intenso, vivo de esa manera.
我在我家的伴侣，这是让我放心并降低我的水平的人。
My partner in my house, which is the one that reassures me and lowers my levels.
mi pareja en mi casa, que es la que me tranquiliza y me baja los niveles.
但是，是的，一般而言，我是这样的，我很激烈，每一刻，我都会朝着最大程度的发展。
But yes, generally I am like that, I am intense and every moment I live it towards the maximum.
Pero sí, generalmente yo soy así, soy intenso y cada momento lo vivo hacia el máximo.
当您说您的伴侣是放心的伴侣时，意味着放屁的伴侣，我想让它免费。
When you say that your partner is the one that reassures you and means the one that farts, let's say, I want to spend it free.
Cuando decís que tu pareja es la que te tranquiliza y quiere decir la que te caga pedos, digamos, lo quiero pasar en libre.
这不是法院吗？
Is this not the court?
¿Esto no es la cancha?
这样的一件事。
One thing like that.
Una cosa así.
当我回到家时，他们告诉我，帕里，你不在足球比赛中，镇定。
When I get home they tell me, paraly, you are not in football, calm.
Cuando llego a casa me dicen, pará, no estás en el fútbol, tranquilo.
安静，然后有点低
Quiet, then a little low
tranquilo, me baja entonces un poco
您在这里，不仅是为了家族史，而且因为您在AtléticoB中玩过，现在您处于最大状态。
You are here, not only for family history, but because you played at Atlético B and now you are in the biggest.
Vos sos de acá, no solo por la historia familiar, sino porque jugaste en el Atlético B y ahora estás en la mayor.
但是所有阿根廷人都被带到了。
But all Argentines were brought.
Pero se trajeron a todos los argentinos.
人们想要很多球员。
There are many players that people want.
Hay muchos jugadores que la gente quiere.
但是，由于那个俱乐部中的阿根廷人和世界冠军，阿根廷人不可能不成为亚特比特托。
But it is impossible for an Argentine not to be Atlético, because of the number of Argentines in that club, and world champions as well.
Pero es imposible que un argentino no sea del Atlético, por la cantidad de argentinos que hay en ese club, y campeones del mundo también.
显然我们是许多阿根廷人，我们是一个乐队...
Obviously we are many Argentines, we are a band ...
Obviamente somos muchos argentinos, somos una banda...
漂亮和内部显然有世界冠军和美国冠军，我们是一个
pretty and inside obviously there are world champion and champions of America and well we are a
linda y adentro obviamente hay campeón del mundo y campeones de América y bueno somos un
一个很好的团队，我们相处得很好，也就是说，我们很有帮助。
A nice group where we get along very well, that is, we help a lot.
Un lindo grupo donde nos llevamos muy bien, o sea, ayudamos un montón.
事实是，我们正在全力以赴。
And the truth is that we are competing to the fullest.
y la verdad que estamos compitiendo al máximo.
格里兹曼给人的感觉也有点阿根廷。
And Griezmann gives the feeling that is also a bit Argentine.
Y Griezmann da la sensación que también es un poco argentino.
我不知道为什么。
I don't know why.
No sé por qué.
看来，对吧？
It seems, right?
Parece, ¿no?
是的，是的，似乎有点阿根廷，这是所有的。
Yes, yes, it seems a bit Argentine, it's a bit of everything.
Sí, sí, parece un poco argentino, es un poco de todo.
他喜欢和阿根廷的口音，伴侣和所有这些都有所在的说话。
He likes to speak as well as in an Argentine accent, the mate and all that is also a little there.
le gusta hablar así como en acento argentino, el mate y todo eso así que también está ahí un poco.
我知道那个精英运动员，就像你的情况一样...
I know that elite athletes, as is your case ...
Yo sé que los deportistas elite, como es tu caso...
事情永远不会引起关注，成就。
Things never attracts attention, achievements.
Nunca le llama la atención las cosas, los logros.
因为他们留下了一切，所以他们一直在职业或训练中，并且总是想达到最大程度。
Because they leave everything, they are in a career or train all the time and always want to get to the maximum.
porque dejan todo, están en toda una carrera o entrenan todo el tiempo y siempre quieren llegar al máximo.
当您生活的那一刻，毫无意义。
There is no point that surprises the moment you are living.
No hay en un punto que te sorprenda el momento que estás viviendo.
当我说这一刻不仅是Atlético的表现如何，而且...
When I say the moment is not only how good Atlético does, but ...
Cuando digo el momento es no solo lo bien que le va al Atlético, sino...
您的表现，交付，人们的爱，认可。
Your performance, delivery, people's love, recognition.
tu rendimiento, la entrega, el cariño de la gente, el reconocimiento.
您能为您提供一点，还是您不仅仅是自我批评？
Can you thank you for a little or you are more than self -criticism?
¿Te agradeces un poquito eso o sos más de la autocrítica?
如果没有，我们应该遵循还是正常？
If not, should we follow or is it normal?
Si no, ¿hay que seguir o es lo normal?
好吧，我通常不仅仅是自我批评，您总是必须给人更多的东西
Well, I am generally more than the self -criticism that you always have to give a little more, that people
Bueno, yo generalmente soy más de la autocrítica de que siempre hay que dar un poco más, de que la gente
您将永远要求一点...
You will always demand a little ...
siempre te va a exigir un poquito...
每天都有更多，昨天不再重要，这总是很重要。
more every day and that yesterday no longer counts and that always counts.
más cada día y que lo de ayer ya no cuenta y que cuenta siempre.
现在，现在和生活
The present, the present and live every day
el hoy, el presente y vivir cada día
所以显然我也感到惊讶。
So obviously I was also surprised.
Así obviamente también me sorprendió todo.
所有这些都在发生。
All this is happening.
todo esto que viene pasando.
正如我告诉您的那样，我专注于一天至一天的培训，我不认为或...
As I told you, I focus on training on a day -to -day basis and I don't think or ...
Como te dije, me centro en entrenar en el día a día y no pienso ni...
在发生的事情或会发生什么。
Neither in what happened, or what will come.
ni en lo que pasó, ni en lo que va a venir.
所以，我那样。
So, well, I'm like that.
Así que, bueno, soy así.
您是否去了意大利队？
Did you proceed to the Italian team?
¿A vos te sondieron para la selección italiana?
你出生在意大利吗？
Did you be born in Italy?
¿Vos naciste en Italia?
我想拥有意大利公民身份。
I imagine having Italian citizenship.
Imagino tener ciudadanía italiana.
你也有吗？
And you also have or not?
¿Y española tenés también o no?
不，我在罗马没有西班牙的阿根廷公民身份。
No, I have Spanish Argentine citizenship, in Rome nothing.
No, yo tengo ciudadanía argentina española, en Roma nada.
不，是否选择西班牙探针？
No, are the selection of Spain probes or not?
No, ¿están sondeados la selección de España o no?
或您到达的第一个电话是阿根廷。
Or the first call that reaches you is Argentina.
O la primera convocatoria que llega a vos es la argentina.
不，不，永远不会...
No, no, never me ...
No, no, nunca me...
他们谈论了西班牙，什么都没有，显然，无论他们谈论了多少西班牙，100％阿根廷。
They talked about Spain and nothing and obviously, no matter how much they talked about Spain, 100% Argentine.
hablaron de España y nada y obviamente por más que me hayan hablado de España, 100% argentino.
您的生日是18岁或12岁的美好事实。
You have a beautiful fact that your birthday is 18 or 12.
Tienes un dato hermoso que es que tu cumpleaños es el 18 o el 12.
你不敢相信。
You can't believe.
No se puede creer.
我的意思是，您将一年转为阿根廷世界冠军。
I mean, you turned year to Argentina world champion.
O sea, cumpliste año Argentina campeona del mundo.
你几岁？
How old were you?
¿Qué edad tenías?
那天你转了几岁？
How old did you turn that day?
¿Qué edad cumpliste ese día?
那天，如果我不感到困惑，他拿了一个剪辑，去了C。
That day, if I did not get confused, he took a clip, went to C.
Ese día, si no me confundo, llevó un clip, fue a C.
两年前。
Two years ago.
Hace dos años.
二十。
Twenty.
Veinte.
二十年。
Twenty years.
Veinte años.
如果您想到这个故事，这很漂亮。
It's pretty, if you think about the story.
Es linda, si te pones a pensar la historia.
是的，那是我的生日。
Yes, it was my birthday.
Sí, era mi cumpleaños.
看到世界的决赛，也就是最好的场景。
Seeing the final of the world, that is, the best possible scenario.
viendo la final del mundo, o sea, el mejor escenario posible.
那天，阿根廷是世界冠军，这是最好的礼物。
And that Argentina just that day comes out world champion, which was the best gift.
y que Argentina justo ese día salga campeón del mundo, que fue el mejor regalo.
生日，我可以拥有。
Birthday I could have.
cumpleaños que podría tener.
第一次打电话给阿根廷国家队的呼吁是如何获得的？
How does the first call to the Argentine National Team get?
¿Cómo te llega la primera convocatoria a la selección argentina?
我在我家镇定的阿根廷国家队的第一个呼吁。
The first call to the Argentine National Team I am in my house, calm.
La primera convocatoria a la Selección Argentina estoy en mi casa, tranquilo.
坐着，给我发了沃尔特的消息。
Sitting and sent me a Walter message.
sentado y me mandó un mensaje Walter.
他告诉我，好吧，我是沃尔特·塞缪尔（Walter Samuel），我想要...
And he told me, well, I'm Walter Samuel, I want ...
Y me dijo, bueno, soy Walter Samuel, quiero...
与您交谈，让我们看看您是否可以打电话给您。
Talk to you, let's see if you can call you.
Hablar con vos, a ver si podés que te llame.
但是，请问。
To, but ask.
Para, pero pregunta.
我想知道这一点。
I want to know this.
Quiero saber esto.
Walters Harmony，我想您必须有欧洲手机，但是您收到一条未知的消息，您没有安排它。
Walters Harmony, I imagine that you must have a European phone, but you get an unknown message, you didn't have it scheduled.
Walters Harmony, imagino que debe tener teléfono europeo, pero a vos te llega un mensaje desconocido, no lo tenías agendado.
不，当然，这尚不清楚，但这让我成为沃尔特·塞缪尔（Walter Samuel）。
No, of course, it gets unknown, but it puts me I am Walter Samuel.
No, claro, me llega desconocido, pero me pone soy Walter Samuel.
是的，我可以打电话给你。
Yes, I can call you.
Si, si puedo llamarte.
在那里您说... 0.5秒，给我打电话。
And there you said ... 0.5 seconds, call me.
Y ahí dijiste... 0,5 segundos, llamame.
0.5秒。
0.5 seconds.
0,5 segundos.
我准备好了。
I'm ready.
Estoy listo.
他打电话给我，当他打电话给我时，我们正在见你，我们在跟随你。
He calls me and when he calls me we were seeing you, we were following you.
Me llama y cuando me llama me dice te estuvimos viendo, te estuvimos siguiendo.
我希望您成为此列表的一部分。
I want you to be part of this list.
Quiero que formes parte de esta lista.
这与阿根廷国家队以及他们要向您发送航班时，一切。
That comes with the Argentine National Team and when they are going to send you the flights, everything.
que viene con la selección argentina y cuando te van a mandar los vuelos, todo.
所以要完美，所以
So to come perfect so
así que para venir perfecto así que en cuanto
我割了，我开始告诉我的家人，我的伴侣我在那里，我们开始...
I cut, I started telling my family, my partner I was there, we started ...
corté, empecé a decir a mi familia, a mi pareja que estaba ahí, empezamos...
我之所以哭泣，是因为在阿根廷国家队里到场真是太疯狂了。
I started crying because it is crazy to be there in the Argentine National Team.
Yo empecé a llorar porque es una locura estar ahí en la Selección Argentina.
凭借全世界的冠军，事实真是一个非常漂亮的幸福。
With all the world champions and the truth was a very pretty happiness.
con todos los campeones del mundo y la verdad fue una felicidad muy linda.
在接触时，您去了电话？
And at the touch you went to the call?
¿Y al toque te fuiste a la convocatoria?
你打电话给你，你什么时候必须去？
Did you call you and when did you have to go?
¿Te llamó y cuándo tenías que ir?
他打电话给我，我认为他们是第二天，我不得不去。
He called me and I think they were the next day and I had to go.
Me llamó y creo que fueron al día siguiente y tenía que ir.
有多美丽，对吗？
How beautiful, right?
Qué hermoso, ¿no?
那是我要去选择的飞行，他们也出现了
And that flight of, I am going to the selection and they also appear
y ese vuelo de, yo estoy yendo a la selección y además te aparecen
出现梅西。
A Messi appears.
Te aparece un Messi.
我想那一刻就像零的一切一样，无论您是世界足球多么死亡。
I imagine that moment is like everything from zero, no matter how much you are the world football to die.
Imagino que ese momento es como todo de cero, por más que vos sos mundo fútbol a morir.
好像，哦，我必须进入该物业，并且有所有这些怪物。
It is as if, oh, I have to enter the property and there are all those monsters.
Es como si, uy, tengo que entrar al predio y están todos esos monstruos.
与...在一起真是太疯狂了
It's crazy to be with ...
Es una locura estar con...
有了所有这些，显然看到它们是最好的。
With all those, obviously see that they are the best.
con todos esos, ver obviamente que son los mejores.
从与他们一起在更衣室里的世界中，与他们一起训练，学习很多。
From the world of being in the locker room with them, training with them, learning a lot.
del mundo de estar en el vestuario con ellos, entrenar con ellos, aprender muchísimo.
他们在每个培训中，如何。
Of them in each training, how they are.
de ellos en cada entrenamiento, en cómo son.
事实是，在那里您已经有七或八天了，您会学到很多东西。
And the truth is that for more you are seven or eight days there, you learn a lot.
y la verdad que por más que estés siete o ocho días ahí, aprendés muchísimo.
你的老妇是霍利拉吗？
Is your old woman Cholula?
¿Tu vieja es cholula tuya?
有时您会看到你们中的任何一个都像一个手柄。
Sometimes you saw that any of you is like a handle.
a veces viste que cualquiera de ustedes está como ahí manija.
是乔拉还是更多挑战您的人？
Is it Cholula or is it more someone who challenges you?
¿Es cholula o es más alguien que te reta?
如果您的行为，我会改善您。
If you behave, I improve you.
Si te portas, te mejoro.
我不知道，想象一个妈妈。
I don't know, imagine a very mom.
No sé, imagina una cosa muy de mamá.
这是三个的杂物。
And it is very cholula of the three.
y es muy cholula de los tres.
儿子做什么，无论麦卡纳做了多少...
What the son does, no matter how much a macana has been done ...
Lo que hace el hijo, por más que se haya hecho una macana...
很好。
It's very nice.
Está muy bien.
这是最好的。
It is the best.
Es el mejor.
愿我儿子决定最好的。
May my son decide the best.
Que mi hijo decida el mejor.
Bancaan All！
Bancaan all!
¡Bancan todas!
是的，是的，是的，是的。
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Sí, sí, sí, sí, sí.
是这样。
It is so.
Es así.
很好。
That is very nice.
Eso es muy lindo.
您的脑海中有2026年世界杯吗？
And do you have the World Cup 2026 in your head?
¿Y vos tenés en la cabeza el Mundial 2026?
最近，您正在选择中，但是很明显，您是Scaloni的雷达。
Recently you are in the selection, but well, clearly in the radar of Scaloni you are.
Hace poco estás en la selección, pero bueno, claramente en el radar de Scaloni estás.
你在那儿，你告诉他，切，一年丢失了。
You have it there, you tell him, che, a year is missing.
Lo tenés ahí, le decís, che, falta un año.
我将尽可能地做这件事。
And I am going to do the thing as well as possible to be there.
Y yo te voy a hacer la cosa lo mejor posible para poder estar ahí.
好吧，让我们看看，这是……这个……到世界杯...
Well, let's see, the truth that ... this ... to the World Cup ...
Bueno, a ver, la verdad que... este... al Mundial...
那真是太疯狂了，对我来说，这将是一个梦。
That comes would be crazy to be there, for me it would be a dream.
que viene sería una locura estar ahí, para mí sería un sueño.
是，我想...
Be, I think ...
estar, creo que...
我想成为，但我必须训练很多。
I want to be but I have to train a lot.
Quiero estar pero tengo que entrenar mucho.
每天，改善许多事情。
In day to day, improve many things.
en el día a día, mejorar muchísimas cosas.
有很多球员
There are a lot of players
Hay un montón de jugadores
非常好，可以成为该列表的一部分，并希望
very good that can be part of that list and hopefully the day that
muy buenos que pueden formar parte de esa lista y ojalá que el día que
那个电话可以到来是因为
that that call can come because
que llegue esa convocatoria pueda estar porque
对我来说，参加世界杯是我的最大梦想。
For me, playing a World Cup is my maximum dream.
Para mí, jugar un Mundial es mi máximo sueño.
您已经参加了选择聊天还是尚未承认？
Are you already in the selection chat or have you not yet admitted?
¿Vos ya estás en el chat de la selección o no has ingresado aún?
有聊天。
There is a chat.
Hay un chat.
不，因为有世界冠军聊天。
No, for, there is a world champions chat.
No, para, hay un chat de campeones del mundo.
我在接受采访中问梅西。
I asked Messi in an interview.
Esto se lo pregunté a Messi en una entrevista.
聊天被称为世界冠军，我不知道是否每次有人添加它。
The chat is called world champions and I don't know if every time someone adds it.
El chat se llama Campeones del Mundo y yo no sé si cada vez que se suma alguien lo van sumando.
不，你没有聊天，我不知道。
No, you don't have a chatter, I don't know.
No, vos no tenés un chatter, no sé.
我没有...我们在这个团队中。
I don't have ... we are here in this team.
No tengo... Nosotros estamos acá en este equipo.
例如，我有一个名为欧洲的聊天。
I have a chat called Europe, for example.
Yo tengo un chat que se llama Viaje a Europa, por ejemplo.
是的，是的，是的。
Yes, yes, yes.
Sí, sí, sí.
我不知道这是怎么回事。
I don't know how it is.
No sé cómo es.
我不知道是谁处理的。
I don't know who handles it.
No sé quién lo maneja.
是的，我知道是谁。
Yes I know who it is.
Sí sé quién es.
par。
Paredes.
Paredes是管理员。
Paredes is the administrator.
Paredes es el administrador.
我不知道选择中有聊天。
I have no idea that there is a chat there from the selection.
No tengo ni idea que hay un chat ahí de la selección.
我是...
I am one of the ...
Yo soy uno de los...
在新的，显然他们要去很多时间都有一个小组
Of the new and obviously they are going to them a lot of time has a group
de los nuevos y obviamente van a ellos están muchísimo tiempo tiene un grupo
武装，我不知道最重要的是我去了两个列表
armed and I have no idea that there is on top I went to two lists
armado y no tengo ni idea que hay encima fui a dos listas
几乎没有缺少，也许不是Garnacho。
Little is missing, maybe it's not garnacho.
Falta poco, tal vez no está garnacho.
我不知道，我不知道。
I don't know, I have no idea.
No sé, no tengo ni idea.
我知道您为Juliánálvare做了很多事情，来到这个俱乐部。
I know that you did a lot for Julián Álvare to come to this club.
Yo sé que vos hiciste mucho para que Julián Álvarez venga a este club.
你做了很多事情，你在灼伤他的头。
You did a lot, you were burning his head a little.
Lo hiciste mucho, le fuiste quemando un poco la cabeza.
他说不，因为我看到了一张笔记，好吧，给我一些通行证。
And he said no, because I saw a note that, well give me something of the pass.
y él dijo que no, porque yo vi una nota que, bueno dame algo del pase.
他说，他不会认识到通行证的一部分。
He said he will not recognize a percentage of the pass.
Dijo que no te va a reconocer un porcentaje del pase.
在奥林匹克运动会中，当我们在那里分享时的真相...
In the Olympic Games, the truth that when we share there ...
En los Juegos Olímpicos, la verdad que cuando compartimos ahí...
他扔了一件事或另一件事去了阿特利特托（Atlético），后者不得不去马德里（Atléticode Madrid）。
He threw one thing or another to go to Atlético, who had to go to Atlético de Madrid.
le tiraba una cosa u otra para que vaya al Atlético, que tenía que ir al Atlético de Madrid.
看到体育场，人，什么是俱乐部。
See everything that was the stadium, people, what is the club.
ver todo lo que era el estadio, la gente, lo que es el club.
意识形态和一切，显然是在...
Ideology and everything, and obviously after ...
la ideología y todo, y obviamente después le...
他投掷了侵略性，投掷了不同的百分比3％。
He threw aggressive, threw a different percentage, 3%.
Le tiraba agresiva, le tiraba un porcentaje distinto, un 3%.
某物？
Something?
¿Algo?
但是当然。
But of course.
Pero claro.
一个本身。
A itself.
Una propiña.
有些东西必须给你。
Something has to give you.
Algo te tiene que dar.
我不知道，新的粗糙度。
I don't know, a new roughness.
No sé, una remeda nueva.
有些东西必须给你。
Something has to give you.
Algo te tiene que dar.
必须给您一些东西，但是现在，学者暂时不可能。
Something has to give you, but no, the academic for now.
Algo te tiene que dar, pero no, el académico por ahora no.
事实是...
The truth is being ...
La verdad que está siendo...
一个伟大的季节，希望能像这样继续下去。
A great season and hopefully continue like this.
una gran temporada y esperemos que siga así.
有一个漂亮的视频，我不知道您是否看到了。
There is a beautiful video, I don't know if you saw it.
Hay un video hermoso, no sé si lo viste.
这就像一个比较，它非常病毒。
That is like a comparison, it is very viral.
que es como una comparación, es muy viral.
我不记得你在冠军赛中拥抱你的老人是一件小事。
That you are very a small thing hugging your old man, I don't remember, in a championship.
que vos estás muy una cosa chiquita abrazando a tu viejo, no me acuerdo, en un campeonato.
突然，您正在为Atlético做一个目标，这很重要。
And suddenly you are making a goal for Atlético, it is important.
y de repente estás haciendo un gol para el Atlético, es importante.
您要看那些东西吗？
Are you to see those things?
¿Sos de ver esas cosas?
因为您在玩前就像粉丝一样来了。
Because you came like a fan before playing.
Porque vos venías como un hincha antes de jugar.
今天，您必须参加比赛，成为11个。
And today you have to play, be among the eleven.
Y hoy te toca jugar, estar entre los once.
您喜欢这些事情还是您也喜欢吗？
Do you like those things or do you as well?
¿Te gustan esas cosas o te dan como así?
我不知道。
I don't know.
No sé.
不，不，是的，是的，我喜欢看，也就是说，显然，当我还是个男孩的时候，我...
No, no, yes, yes, I like to see, that is, obviously, when I was a boy, I ...
No, no, sí, sí, me gusta ver, o sea, obviamente, cuando era chico, yo...
我知道那段视频是什么，我认为我可以到达。
I know what that video is, which I think I am from reaching.
Sé cuál es ese vídeo, que creo que estoy de Alcanzapelota.
是的，你去拥抱他。
Yes, you go and hug him.
Sí, vas y lo abrazas.
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
不，辣，分开。
No, spicy, apart.
No, picante, aparte.
从那时起我认识你。
I know you from that time.
Yo te conozco de esa época.
这与皇家马德里有关。
It went against Real Madrid.
fue contra el Real Madrid.
显然在那里伸到他的球。
Obviously being there reaches him balls.
Obviamente estar ahí le alcanza pelotas.
很久以前的一切都是T1马德里，今天我必须在这里。
Everything that was the T1 Madrid a long time ago and today I have to be here.
todo lo que fue la T1 Madrid hace bastante tiempo y hoy me toca estar acá.
与伟大的球员一起玩。
Playing with great players.
jugando con grandes jugadores.
前几天，他实现了目标是一个愉快的时光。
And the other day he made a goal was a nice time.
y el otro día que hizo un gol fue un lindo momento.
考虑到您的姓氏，一个人的压力更大，在这种情况下，您的老人是老人的技术人员，您在Atlético中踢球。
One has more pressure taking into account your last name, in this case your old man is the old man's technician and you play in Atlético.
Uno tiene más presión teniendo en cuenta tu apellido, en este caso puntualmente tu viejo es el técnico del Atlético y vos jugás en el Atlético.
她在陈述中清楚地表明了一千次，几乎一半的人在被问及时会热身，他是一名球员，如果他不要离开，他就表现良好。
She made clear a thousand times in the statements, almost half that he warms up when asked, he is a player, if he plays well, if he is not going to leave.
Ella dejó claro mil veces en las declaraciones, casi que medio que se calienta cuando le preguntan, es un jugador, si juega bien va a entrar, si no va a salir.
您的压力更大，所以这是我的感觉。
You have more pressure so because this is my feeling.
Vos tenés más presión por eso porque de afuera esta es mi sensación.
我说，情况恰恰相反，这是一个必须付出更多的孩子，因为眼睛会戴在他身上。
I say, it is quite the opposite, it is a kid who has to give more because the eyes will be put on him.
Yo digo, es todo lo contrario, es un pibe que tiene que dar más porque los ojos van a estar puestos en él.
这是我的感觉，也许我错了。
This is my feeling, maybe I'm wrong.
Esta es mi sensación, tal vez estoy equivocado.
好吧，让我们看看，自从我在这里开始采石场以来
Well, let's see, since I started the quarry here in the
Bueno, a ver, yo desde que empecé la cantera acá en el
在马德里的阿特利特托·德·马德里（Atléticode Madrid），在河流的学校，河中的下部。
In Atlético de Madrid, in the school in River, the lower ones in River.
en el Atlético de Madrid, en la escuelita en River, las inferiores en River.
在Zaragoza的通行证，在Alavés，我有很多技术人员
The pass in Zaragoza, in Alavés I had many technicians where
El pase en Zaragoza, en el Alavés tuve muchos técnicos donde
他们总是要求球员给
They always demand that their players give the
siempre exigen a sus jugadores dar el
最大的，当我总是尝试这样做时，显然是教练
the maximum and when I always try to do it that obviously the coach
el máximo y cuando yo trato siempre de hacerlo que obviamente el entrenador
要求给球队最大值。
Ask to give the team the maximum.
pide para darle al equipo lo máximo.
最大可能的性能
maximum possible performance and from
máximo rendimiento posible y a partir de
从那里开始，我认为我们既是专业人士又是专注于马德里运动盾牌时的专注。
From there I think we are both professionals and we focus when we are with the Athletic Shield of Madrid.
De ahí creo que los dos somos profesionales y nos centramos cuando estamos con el Escudo Atlético de Madrid.
我们工作。
We work.
Trabajamos.
我了解这一点，但我不是那么专业。
I understand it, but I am not so professional.
Yo lo entiendo, pero yo no soy tan profesional.
然后，我想，假设情况来自明天的比赛，再生。
Then I imagine, suppose the situation, come from playing tomorrow, regenerative.
Entonces yo imagino, suponete la situación, vienen de jugar mañana, regenerativo.
20，给爸爸，我会逃脱我，你仍然不能，给我，离开我...
20, give dad, I would escape me yet, you still can't, give it, leave me ...
20, dale papá, yo se me escaparía aún, aún no se puede, dale, déjame...
不，你不能。
No, you can't.
No, no se puede eso.
在这里你不能。
Here you can't.
Acá no se puede.
我一进入Cerro del Espino ...
As soon as I enter the Cerro del Espino ...
En cuanto entro al Cerro del Espino…
我简直不敢相信。
I can't believe it.
No lo puedo creer.
不，我可以相信，但是我知道帽子会多么。
No, I can believe it, but I know how Chapear would.
No, sí lo puedo creer, pero yo sé cómo chapearía.
哦，爸爸！
Oh, dad!
¡Ay, papá!
不，你不能。
No, you can't.
No, eso no se puede.
那不能。
That can't.
Eso no se puede.
和您的目标？
And objectives you have?
¿Y objetivos que tenés?
您已经说过世界杯将是您的梦想。
You already said that the World Cup would be your dream.
Ya dijiste que el Mundial sería tu sueño.
我想，用Atlético实现了目标。
And achieve things with Atlético, I imagine.
Y lograr cosas con el Atlético, imagino.
显然目标是与Atlético在一起。
Obviously objectives, be with Atlético.
Obviamente objetivos, estar con el Atlético.
尽可能多地给这个俱乐部，因为他们做了很多
as much as possible, I want to give this club because they did a lot
lo máximo posible, a este club le quiero dar todo porque hicieron mucho
对我来说，显然，希望有一天
For me and obviously, hope someday
por mí y obviamente, ojalá algún día
能够在这个俱乐部赢得一些东西。
To be able to win something with this club.
poder ganar algo con este club.
显然，总是会尽我所能。
And always, obviously, give everything I can.
y siempre, obviamente, darle todo lo que pueda a mí.
我的100％永远是。
My 100% will always be.
Mi 100% va a estar siempre.
你在河里玩了吗？
Did you play in River?
¿Vos jugaste en River?
明天的河流人会感到兴奋，如果您参加阿根廷足球比赛，那就在那里踢球吗？
Can the people of River tomorrow be excited that if you play in Argentine football, play there?
¿La gente de River el día de mañana se puede ilusionar con que si vos jugás en el fútbol argentino juegues ahí?
否则它更开放，其他俱乐部也有可能。
Or it is more open, there are possibilities of other clubs.
o está más abierto, hay posibilidades de otros clubes.
我说的是，有几年，但是您已经穿过河。
I am talking, there are a few years, but you have passed through the River.
Estoy hablando, faltan unos cuantos años, pero has pasado por el River.
是的，当然，显然。
Yes, of course, obviously.
Sí, claro, obviamente.
我在学校里穿过河流。
I went through River in the school, in the lower ones.
Yo pasé por River en la escuelita, en las inferiores.
来自里弗（River），我也非常感谢他们给了我
From River, where I am also very grateful that they gave me
de River, donde también estoy muy agradecido que me dieron
许多工具，我开始在那儿玩很多工具，在较低的工具中是一个联盟。
Many tools, I started playing there a lot, in the lower ones that is a league.
Muchísimas herramientas, empecé a jugar ahí mucho, en las inferiores que es liga.
和AFA以及许多对我有很多帮助的同事，教练。
And AFA and with many colleagues who helped me a lot, coaches.
Y AFA y con muchos compañeros que me ayudaron mucho, entrenadores.
许多人也在预备役中训练。
A lot of people also training in the reserve.
un montón de gente entrenando también en la reserva.
我很高兴通过该过程。
I am very happy to have passed that process.
Estoy muy contento de haber pasado ese proceso.
将来我可以在那里。
In the future I can be there.
en un futuro pueda estar ahí.
我的意思是，这是一个受到影响的俱乐部。
It is a club that is affected, I mean.
Es un club que le tienes cariño, eso me refiero.
是的，很多爱。
Yes, a lot of love.
Sí, mucho cariño.
我从哪里开始。
Where I started.
Donde empecé.
不，这很好，但是很明显，如果必须识别，您就是来自马德里的Atléticode。
No, it's fine, but clearly if one has to identify, you are a person from Atlético de Madrid.
No, está bien, pero claramente si uno se tiene que identificar, vos sos una persona del Atlético de Madrid.
因为您几乎一生都住在这里，但是是的，在阿根廷，您喜欢河。
Because you lived here almost all your life, but yes, in Argentina you like River.
Porque viviste acá casi toda tu vida, pero sí, en Argentina te gusta River.
是的，是的。
Yes, yes.
Sí, sí.
好，完美。
Well, perfect.
Bien, perfecto.
要结束我们有测试。
To close we have a test.
Para cerrar tenemos un test.
我们将其称为测试类似。
We call this the test Simession.
Este lo llamamos el test simione.
不要假装你父亲，而是为你们所有人。
Do not pretend for your dad, but for all of you.
No simione por tu papá, sino por todos ustedes.
我要问你几个问题，然后就可以回答我。
I'm going to ask you a couple of questions and you answer me as long as you want.
Yo te voy a hacer un par de preguntas y vos me respondés siempre y cuando quieras.
如果您不告诉我，请进行逻辑。
If you don't tell me, take the logical.
Si no me decís, tomate la, logico.
好吧？
Alright?
¿Está bien?
完美的。
Perfect.
Perfecto.
准备好了吗？
Is it prepared?
¿Está preparado?
完美的。
Perfect.
Perfecto.
好，完美。
Well, perfect.
Bien, perfecto.
模拟测试。
Simes test.
Test de los simiones.
谁是最好的比赛？
Who is the best play?
¿Quién es el que mejor juega?
整个家庭。
Of the whole family.
De toda la familia.
整个家庭？
Of the whole family?
¿De toda la familia?
好吧，你的老人退休了，但是谁是最好的戏？
Ok, your old man is retired, but who is the best play?
Vale, tu viejo está retirado, pero ¿quién es el que mejor juega?
好吧，我认为这是乔瓦尼。
Well, I think it's Giovanni.
Bueno, yo creo que es Giovanni.
乔瓦尼。
Giovanni.
我认为是实现最大目标的人。
I think it is the one who made the most goals.
Creo que es el que más goles hizo de la familia.
对我来说是乔瓦尼。
For me it is Giovanni.
Para mí es Giovanni.
好，完美。
Well, perfect.
Bien, perfecto.
谁是球场上最混蛋？
Who is the most bastard on the court?
¿Quién es el más cabrón en la cancha?
我的老人更混蛋。
My old man is more bastard.
Es más cabrón mi viejo.
好的。
GOOD.
Bien.
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
温暖的
Warm
Calentón.
温暖的
Warm
Calentón.
我放了代码，与你说话，我的老人，百分百
I put the code, speak to you, my old man, one hundred percent
te mete el código, te habla, mi viejo, cien por cien
好，完美。
Well, perfect.
Bien, perfecto.
谁是球场外最友好的人？
Who is the most bastard outside the court?
¿Quién es el más cabrón fuera de la cancha?
哟
Yo
啊，是吗？
Ah, yes?
Ah, ¿sí?
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
在许多情况下，我有点搞砸了。
I am a bit screwed in many situations.
Soy un poco jodido en bastantes situaciones.
但是，例如，我想理解，我在你身后，你看到了吗？
But what, for example, I want to understand, I am behind you, did you see?
Pero qué, por ejemplo, quiero entender, estoy atrás tuyo, ¿viste?
这些人打扰我，喇叭，喇叭。
These people bother me, horn, horn.
Esa gente me da molestia, bocina, bocina.
你可以热身。
You can warm up.
Te podés llegar a calentar.
没有角。
No touch of horn.
No toque de bocina.
我在家庭中也有点像这样。
I am also a bit like that in the family.
Yo en la familia también soy un poco así.
提出要点的人。
The one who puts the points.
El que pone los puntos.
男孩，不是。
Boys, not.
Chicos, esto no.
好，完美。
Well, perfect.
Bien, perfecto.
圣诞节在圣诞节的跳动？
The bush's beat at Christmas?
¿El beat del tonel en Navidad?
不。
No.
谁放更好的外观？
Who puts better looks?
¿Quién mete mejores looks?
谁看到了整个家庭中最好的？
Who saw the best of the whole family?
¿Quién viste mejor de toda la familia?
我相信那里是让·卢卡斯（Jean-Lucas）。
I believe that there Jean-Lucas.
Yo creo que ahí Jean-Lucas.
好的。
GOOD.
Bien.
现在如何使用社交网络？
How is it now with social networks?
¿Cómo está ahora con las redes sociales?
他正在进入。
He is getting into.
Se está metiendo.
他有脸，你看到了吗？
He has a face, did you see?
Tiene facha, ¿viste?
我认为那…
I think that…
Yo creo que…
他用长发，短发，然后塑造，很好。
He used long hair, short hair, then shaped, it was very good.
usó pelo largo, pelo corto, después se rapó, le quedó muy bien.
我认为他是最好的。
I think he is the best.
Yo creo que él es el que mejor le queda.
您也看到了很好。
You also saw it well.
También lo viste bien.
您看到Fachera的人给我一点愤怒。
You saw that fachera people give me a little anger.
Viste que la gente fachera, esto me da un poco de bronca.
一直以来，他都会剪发，他改变了，因为他知道一切看起来都不错。
All the time cuts his hair, he changes because he knows that everything looks good.
Todo el tiempo se corta los pelos, va cambiando porque sabe que todo le queda bien.
是的，看起来不错。
Yes, it looks good.
Sí, le queda bien.
我的兄弟剃光了，很好。
My brother shaved and it was good.
Mi hermano se rapó y le quedó bien.
你看起来不错吗？
Do you look good?
¿Te queda bien?
我给勃朗卡
I give bronca
Me da bronca
人们知道。
People know.
La gente sabe.
谁是最浪漫的？
Who is the most romantic?
¿Quién es el más romántico?
它也可以是亲切的，就像那个蓬勃发展的人一样。
It can also be affectionate, like that person who throws hearts.
Puede ser cariñoso también, como esa persona que tira corazones.
我更浪漫。
I am more romantic.
Yo, yo soy más romántico.
我知道我的兄弟和我的老人。
I know my brothers and my old man.
Que conozco a mis hermanos y a mi viejo.
在这样的夫妻中，我认为我更浪漫。
Of the couples like that, I think I'm more romantic.
De las parejas así, yo creo que soy más romántico.
我喜欢你。
I like that of you.
Me gusta eso de vos.
谁是最重要的？
Who is the most mamero?
¿Quién es el más mamero?
这不是你的老人。
Here is not your old man.
Acá no entra tu viejo.
谁是谁妈妈，妈妈，妈妈，妈妈？
Who is the one who mom, mom, mom, mom?
¿Quién es el que mamá, mamá, mamá, mamá?
那一个离开了乔亚尼。
The one leaves Joani.
El uno le dejo a Joani.
是的？
Yeah?
¿Sí?
很远。
Very far.
Lejísimo.
但是什么级别？
But what levels?
¿Pero qué niveles?
我们一分钟前聊了。
We talked a minute ago.
Hablamos hace un minuto.
不，也就是说，他们说，是的，我妈妈很多，但是有一个问题...
No, that is, they speak, yes, with my mom a lot, but there is a problem ...
No, o sea, que hablan, sí, con mi mamá bastante, pero si hay un problema...
总是拉，您会看到，好的，或者是，好的，或者看...
Always pull, you see, the good one, or yes, okay, or look ...
siempre tira, viste, la del buen, o sí, está bien, o fíjate...
好吧，毫无疑问。
Ok, well, no doubt.
Ok, bien, sin duda.
还有两个。
There are two left.
Quedan dos.
谁是家庭聊天中最活跃的人？
Who is the most active in the family chat?
¿Quién es el más activo en el chat familiar?
Sanluga。
Sanluga.
他从来没有说他说的更多，他更多地使用电话。
He never says he speaks more, he is more with the phone.
Ya nunca dice que habla más, está más con el teléfono.
提出。
Proposes.
Propone.
提议，是的。
Proposes things, yes.
Propone cosas, sí.
就像，你好，他们要去什么？
Like, Hello, what are they going?
Como, hola, ¿qué andan?
是的，是的，是的。
Yes, yes, yes.
Sí, sí, sí.
最好经常回应一次。
Better respond once every so often.
Mejor responde una vez cada tanto.
好吧，我明白。
Okay, I understand.
Está bien, entiendo.
最后，如果有人这样做，谁做得最好。
And the last, if anyone does, who does the best roasts.
Y lo último, si es que alguno hace, quién hace los mejores asados.
我的老人。
My old man.
Mi viejo.
我的老人是做最好的烤肉的人。
My old man is the one who makes the best roasts.
Mi viejo es el que hace los mejores asados.
当然，他是一个放着爱的人。
Surely, he is a guy who puts love.
Seguro, es un tipo que le pone donde le pone amor.
它也适用于15个人。
It also does for 15 people.
También hace para 15 personas.
一组被拧紧的团体。
A large group that is screwed.
Un grupo grande que es jodido.
不，当然，因为您站在四个进入进入和散步的情况下。
No, of course, because you stand four do an entrance and walk.
No, claro, porque parado cuatro haces una entrañita y caminas.
当然，四个，你看到了吗？
Of course, four, did you see?
Claro, cuatro, ¿viste?
Mocheja，Chori ... 15岁，您拿了一些东西，您不必燃烧。
Mocheja, Chori ... for 15, you take something and you have not to burn.
Mocheja, chori... Para 15, sacas algo y no se te tiene que quemar.
有些人以一种肉的方式吃东西，有些人从另一种肉吃东西，您看到了吗？
And some eat in one way of meat, others eat from another, did you see?
Y algunos comen de una manera de carne, otros comen de otra, ¿viste?
在这里玩。
And here playing.
Y aquí jugando.
这是一个可怕的才华。
It is a terrible talent.
Es un talento terrible.
而且，那些人...对不起，这已经是一次演讲。
Moreover, those people ... sorry, this is already a talk.
Es más, esa gente... Perdón, esto ya es una charla.
那些给我愤怒的人...
Those people who give me anger ...
Esa gente que me da bronca...
他坐着，烤在后面，不压力他，你看到了吗？
He sits and the roast behind and does not stress him, did you see?
se sienta y el asado atrás y no le estresa, ¿viste?
喜欢...不，是的，保持冷静。
Like ... no, yes, stay calm.
Como que... No, sí, quédate tranquilo.
是的，是的，他在那里吃饭。
Yes, yes, he is eating there.
Sí, sí, está comiendo ahí.
不，很好，很好，有游戏，后面后面有侧面，他得到了控制。
No, calm that is fine, there is the game and has it sideways behind the back, he has it controlled.
No, tranquilo que está bien, está el juego y lo tiene de reojo a la espalda, lo tiene controlado.
好吧，那时，已经批准了，准备就绪。
Well, well, approved then, ready.
Bien, bien, aprobado entonces, listo.
Simones测试已批准。
The simones test is approved.
El test de los simones está aprobado.
你还记得你第一次见到狮子座吗？
Do you remember the first time you saw Leo?
¿Te acordás de la primera vez que viste a Leo?
»梅西？
¿A Messi?
是的，我第一次见到他。
Yes, the first time I saw him.
Sí, la primera vez que lo vi.
正是当我在马德里亚特里特托·德·德·马德里（Atléticode Madrid）的时候，他有长发。
It was when I was here in Atlético de Madrid, that he had long hair.
fue cuando estuve acá en el Atlético de Madrid, que él tenía el pelo largo.
那就是他们在埃尔卡尔德隆（ElCalderón）赢得了马德里竞技队的2比1赢得目标。
which was that they won 2 to 1 in El Calderón to Atletico Madrid who makes a goal.
que fue que le ganaron 2 a 1 en el Calderón a Atletico Madrid que hace un gol.
我假设从左侧到右侧的角度的胸衣并拍照。
I assume the curtuba from the left side to the angle to the right side and take a picture.
que le asumo la cortuba desde el lado izquierdo al ángulo al lado derecho y que me saque una foto.
我简直不敢相信。
And I couldn't believe it.
y no lo podía creer.
没有对话，您只是要求一张照片。
There were no dialogue, you just asked for a photo.
No hubiste un diálogo, solo le pediste una foto.
是的，这是他何时成为巴塞罗那球员的照片。
Yes, it is a photo of when he was the Barcelona player.
Sí, es una foto de cuando era el jugador de Barcelona.
前几天，您在选择中看到了它。
And the other day you saw it in the selection.
Y el otro día lo viste en la selección.
如果您认为，那真是太疯狂了。
If you think, it's very crazy.
Si te ponés a pensar, es muy loco.
也许不，因为你是运动员，但是...
Maybe no, because you are athlete, but ...
Tal vez que no, porque vos sos deportista, pero...
在照片中，你好，你好，你好吗？一切好吗？或伴侣，这是疯狂的。
Of that, of the photo A, Hello, how are you?, Everything good?, Or a mate, is crazy.
De eso, de la foto a, hola, ¿cómo estás?, ¿todo bien?, o un mate, es loco.
是的，我几乎与他交谈。
Yes, I talked almost anything with him.
Sí, no hablé casi nada con él.
世界上最好的，也有帮助
The best in the world and also helps
el mejor del mundo y ayuda mucho también a
当我们到达国家队时，给年轻人。
To young people when we arrive at the National Team.
a los jóvenes cuando llegamos a la selección.
整合良好的...
to integrate well and the whole presence of ...
a integrarnos bien y toda la presencia de...
从他那里训练时，这是最大的。
From him it is the maximum when you are training there.
de él para nosotros es lo máximo cuando estás entrenando ahí con él.
谢谢，朱利安。
Thanks, Julian.
Gracias, Juliano.
太感谢了。
Thank you so much.
Muchas gracias.
谢谢你。
Thanks to you.
Gracias a vos.